http://www.toasted-cheese.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to primary content
Who we are
Toasted Cheese is an independent, nonprofit literary journal and writing community that was established in January 2001. Our primary website address is: http://www.toasted-cheese.com; the literary journal address is http://tclj.toasted-cheese.com
You can contact the editors at editors@toasted-cheese.com
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on www.toasted-cheese.com we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on www.toasted-cheese.com you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
We will not share the email address or other information associated with your comments or www.toasted-cheese.com account with any outside parties for anything other than legal reasons.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment on www.toasted-cheese.com, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on www.toasted-cheese.com, we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on www.toasted-cheese.com, or have left comments, you can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
“Personal data” refers to data attached to your comments or your www.toasted-cheese.com account, if you have one, and its associated comments and forum posts.
If you have had work published in the literary journal (tclj.toasted-cheese.com), you can request to update or delete the email address or social media information in your bio. Published work will not be removed from tclj.toasted-cheese.com under any circumstances (see submission guidelines).
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Contact information
If you have privacy-related concerns, contact the editors: editors@toasted-cheese.com
Additional information
How we protect your data
If you leave a comment on www.toasted-cheese.com without an account, your email address will not be published. If you choose to make an account, your email address will not be published.
We do include email addresses in the bios of authors published in the literary journal (tclj.toasted-cheese.com) so anyone wishing to contact them can do so directly. We take reasonable precautions to prevent spam bots from accessing email addresses. We don’t use live email links and the @ is replaced with [at] in email addresses to foil spam bots. Authors can request their email address not be published.
Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window)MoreClick to share on Tumblr (Opens in new window)Click to share on Reddit (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pocket (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to print (Opens in new window)
Follow
Follow Toasted Cheese
Get every new post delivered to your Inbox
Join other followers:
